// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Who developed Python Programming Language?",
    answer: "Guido van Rossum",
    options: [
      "Guido van Rossum",
      "Wick van Rossum",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf",
      "Niene Stom"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
    answer: "No",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Machine dependent",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?",
    answer: ".py",
    options: [
      ".py",
      ".p",
      ".pI",
      ".python"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?",
    answer: "Indentation",
    options: [
      "Brackets",
      "Indentation",
      "Keys",
      "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which keyword is used for function in Python language?",
    answer: "Def",
    options: [
      "Function",
      "Def",
      "Fun",
      "Define"
    ]
  },
  

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at runtime, using a construct called __________",
    answer: "lambda",
    options: [
      "anonymous",
      "pi",
      "tuples",
      "lambda"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following functions is a built-in function in python?",
    answer: "print()",
    options: [
      "print()",
      "seed()",
      "factorial()",
      "sqrt()"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one of the following is not a keyword in Python language?",
    answer: "Eval",
    options: [
      "Pass",
      "Eval",
      "Assert",
      "Nonlocal"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the maximum possible length of an identifier in Python?",
    answer: "none of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "79 characters",
      "63 characters",
      "51 characters",
      "none of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is output of print(math.pow(3, 2))?",
    answer: "9.0",
    options: [
      "9",
      "8",
      "9.0",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
  
];